RG 062:102, Town of North Stonington
Connecticut State Library
Town of North Stonington records
1810-1932
Connecticut State Library
North Stonington (Conn.)
10.5 cubic feet
Administrative, election, school, military and tax records for the town of North Stonington.
RG062_102
T000294
Historical Note
The town of North Stonington was incorporated in May 1807 and was taken from Stonington.
Scope and Content
Administrative, election, school, military and tax records for the town of North Stonington.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Elections -- Connecticut -- North Stonington -- Statistics; Voting -- Connecticut -- North Stonington -- Statistics; School enrollment -- Connecticut -- North Stonington -- Statistics; Schools -- Connecticut -- North Stonington -- History -- Sources; Tax assessment -- Connecticut -- North Stonington -- Registers; Taxation -- Connecticut -- North Stonington -- Registers; Local taxation -- Connecticut -- North Stonington -- Registers; Property tax -- Connecticut -- North Stonington -- Registers
Places:
North Stonington (Conn.) -- Records and correspondence; North Stonington (Conn.) -- Statistics, Vitals
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Records, 1810-1932
  - Vote returns, 1827-1850 (Box Box 1)
  - Military service certificates and records pertaining to support of soldiers' families, 1826-1865 (Box Box 1)
  - Town meeting resolutions and notes, 1861-1898 (Box Box 1)
  - Bank statements of stock held, 1863-1865 (Box Box 1)
  - Tax abatements, 1827-1885 (Box Box 1)
  - Marriage certificates, 1836-1850 (Box Box 1)
  - School returns, school visitors' reports, assessment records, 1836-1890 (Box Box 2)
  - Fifth School District records, 1827-1896 (Box Box 2)
  - Fifteenth School District records, 1844-1909 (Box Box 2)
  - Individual tax lists, 1826-1891 (Box Box 3)
  - Tax abstracts, 1810, 1812-1818, 1821-1824, 1826-1831, 1833, 1835-1836, 1838-1839, 1843-1846, 1849-1850 (Box Box 4)
  - Tax abstracts
    Boxes 5, 6, and 14 are on oversize shelving.
    - 1851, 1852, 1853, 1854, 1855, 1856, 1857, 1858, 1859 (Box Box 5)
    - 1860, 1861, 1862, 1863, 1864, 1865 (Box Box 6)
    - 1866, 1867, 1868, 1869, 1870, 1871 (Box Box 7)
    - 1872, 1873, 1874, 1875, 1876, 1877, 1878, 1879 (Box Box 8)
    - 1880, 1881, 1882, 1883, 1884, 1885 (Box Box 9)
    - 1886, 1887, 1888, 1889 (Box Box 10)
    - 1892, 1893, 1894, 1895, 1896 (Box Box 11)
    - 1897, 1898, 1899, 1900, 1901, 1902, 1903 (Box Box 12)
    - 1904, 1905, 1906, 1907, 1908, 1909, 1910 (Box Box 13)
    - 1911, 1912, 1913, 1914, 1915, 1916, 1917, 1932 (Box Box 14)